"focus": "Tools, tips, and techniques for supporting individuals learning to use the internet safely and confidently."
"description": "Training, resources, and support provided to frontline staff and volunteers in partner organizations to equip them to teach digital literacy to community members.",
"participants_trained_2024_2025": 262,
"training_curriculum_modules": [
{
"module": "DC Core",
"duration": "1 hour",
},
{
"module": "Digital Champions for Newcomers (DC4NC)",
"duration": "1 hour",
"focus": "Helping newcomers to Canada develop essential digital competencies."
},
{
"module": "Deep Dive Sessions",
.5 hours",
"focus": "Specialized topics including Employability: Skills for the Workforce, Pathways to Employment, DC Support for Seniors, and DC Support for Youth."
},
{
"module": "Short Shots",
"duration": "30–45 minutes",
"focus": "Targeted topics including Introduction to Chromebooks, AI & Digital Inclusion, and Digital Skills & Social Media."
}
],
